today we have to cover quite a lot of
今天我们必须涵盖很多
ground we will actually begin with
地面，我们实际上将开始
spring boot today and the first thing I
今天的春季靴子，我的第一件事
want to talk about is the spring facet
要谈的是春天
configuration which is very necessary to
配置是非常必要的
set up the springs forth in your
在你的身上架起弹簧
application in your projects and
在您的项目中的应用
IntelliJ and just a new feature which is
IntelliJ和只是一个新功能是
much nicer now in the 2016 door to
现在进入2016年的大门好多了
update when it comes to auto-detected
自动检测时更新
configurations so what our Auto
配置，所以我们的汽车
Detective configuration stay our setup
侦探配置保留我们的设置
switch IntelliJ IDEA can recognize
开关IntelliJ IDEA可以识别
automatically and that covers spring
自动覆盖弹簧
boot applications as well as spring MVC
引导应用程序以及spring MVC
applications you don't need to setup
您不需要设置的应用程序
those automatic manually in your spring
那些在春天自动手动
facet and the new thing in IntelliJ 2016
方面和IntelliJ 2016中的新事物
is that there is a fix to setup default
是否有设置默认值的修复程序
context I'm sorry I need to switch back
抱歉，我需要切换回
to dat forward resolution here as a
在这里提出决议
problem with text to see and there's a
看文字的问题，有一个
quick fix which creates default context
快速修复，可创建默认上下文
which by default includes all the
默认情况下，其中包括所有
available swing configuration files
可用的挥杆配置文件
IntelliJ formed a new project and there
IntelliJ组成了一个新项目，
was always a problem because that makes
一直是一个问题，因为这使得
up with D files which should be covered
D文件应包含在内
by the auto detection process and this
通过自动检测过程
has been fixed norm 2602 so when I
已固定为2602号规范
create on this create default context
在此创建默认上下文上创建
here in the notification I will actually
在通知中，我实际上
get a warning up here which tells me
在这里得到警告，告诉我
that IntelliJ formed an auto detected
IntelliJ形成自动检测
context of type spring mood I have a
我有一个春天心情类型的上下文
spring sample application here and it
春季示例应用程序及其
will actually just create the facet and
实际上只会创建构面，
let all the auto detective file sets be
让所有自动检测文件集为
added to that automatically and now I
自动添加到现在
can open the facet here and I can
可以在这里打开构面，我可以
already see that the spring
已经看到春天了
application context has been auto
应用程序上下文是自动的
detected and if necessary I then can add
检测到，如有必要，我可以添加
any other files to my own manually
手动将其他任何文件
configured context but it will not
配置的上下文，但不会
interfere those auto configured files
干扰那些自动配置的文件
with the order created context ok
与订单创建上下文确定
another small detail but still I think
另一个小细节，但我仍然认为
it's quite nice when you use teespring
当您使用teespring时非常不错
initializer wizard to create a new
初始化向导创建一个新的
Springwood project just using the
Springwood项目仅使用
defaults here and when you select the
默认值在这里，当您选择
starters we have now the stop an area
首先，我们现在停止一个区域
where you can select the Springwood
您可以在其中选择Springwood
version up here you can collapse and
版本在这里你可以崩溃，
expand all the available starters here
在此处展开​​所有可用的启动器
to make it easier to browse them or you
使浏览它们或您更容易
can use the search field here and it
可以在这里使用搜索字段
will highlight all matching stars just
只会突出显示所有匹配的星星
like you are used from the setting
就像您被设置所使用
search and the nice thing is when you
搜索，好事情是当你
for example go back to an older version
例如回到较旧的版本
of spring would like do you wonder tree
春天的时候你想知道树吗
release some stars might not be
释放一些星星可能不会
available in that version and when you
在该版本中以及当您
just hover over those stars you will see
只需将鼠标悬停在这些星星上，您就会看到
a tooltip which not only gives you a bit
工具提示，不仅可以给您一点
normal description of what the star is
关于恒星的一般描述
about but also show you what spring
关于，还告诉你什么春天
would version is required for just star
仅星号需要版本
to be available in your project so
可以在您的项目中使用
that's a nice way to find out why
这是找出原因的好方法
something is not available so maybe
有些东西不可用，所以也许
Stefan can tell us a bit more what what
Stefan可以告诉我们更多些什么
is what is new in Springwood 1.4 which
是Springwood 1.4中的新功能
has been released like just last week is
就像上周一样被释放了
that correct
那个正确
so spring boot 1.4 was released last
因此，Spring Boot 1.4最后发布了
week indeed you can see on the top there
一周的确可以在顶部看到
is this reactive web experimental
这是反应性的网络实验吗
starter so what we're trying to do with
入门者，所以我们试图做的是
it is to allow you to try the new
是为了让您尝试新的
reactive initiative using Spring
使用Spring的反应性主动
Framework 5 so we've released the first
框架5，所以我们发布了第一个
milestone last week as well
也是上周的里程碑
so if you want to try that early access
因此，如果您想尝试这种抢先体验
you can do so and we also added a couple
您可以这样做，我们还添加了一些
of new sequence tour support it won't
新的序列巡视支持将不会
fall so mainly that sched base and new
下降得如此之快，以至于基础和新
for JS so you can you can find them now
对于JS，这样您就可以现在找到它们
in the in the starter with it we've also
在入门中，我们还
added a bunch of new features and
添加了许多新功能，
whatnot phone like failure analyzer so
像故障分析仪这样的手机
it's the if your spring boot application
这是您的spring boot应用程序
fails to start we analyze the exception
无法启动，我们分析异常
and we try to give you a dedicated error
我们会尝试给您一个专门的错误
message we also improve a lot the
消息我们也改善了很多
testing support with slicing so the
切片测试支持，因此
ability to only start part of your
只能开始一部分的能力
context and focus on only one layer of
并仅关注其中的一层
your application so for instance you
您的应用程序，例如
could have a test that's using mock MVC
可能有一个使用模拟MVC的测试
for each controller and it's that's
对于每个控制器，就是这样
going only to load the context for that
只会为此加载上下文
particular controller we've known that
我们知道的特定控制器
for many things like you have the same
对于很多事情，例如你有相同的
for the data layer with the data API
使用数据API的数据层
test we have that for pure rest client
测试我们有纯粹的休息客户
with the rest client and sanitation and
其余的客户和卫生设施以及
there is more than that and in in in
还有不止于此
generally the testing support is much
通常测试支持很多
easier to configure it all ok thanks not
更容易配置，一切都很好，谢谢
Stefan for that update
斯特凡的更新
um everyone should really go and try out
嗯，每个人都应该去尝试一下
the new 1.4 features another last small
新1.4的另一个小巧之处
bit about the spring initialize of
关于春天的一点初始化
wizard when we go back to the first page
向导，当我们回到第一页
you can select between maven and Gradle
您可以在Maven和Gradle之间进行选择
projects and now when you create a
项目，现在当您创建一个
greater project IntelliJ IDEA will also
更大的项目IntelliJ IDEA也将
automatically add the necessary
自动添加必要的
Springfest automatically to your project
Springfest自动添加到您的项目
so that's the same support we had for
所以这就是我们对
the maven project for a long time same
长期以来的Maven项目
stuff not working for greater so now I
东西不工作更大，所以现在我
can switch to the presentation mode
可以切换到演示模式
going to the application properties
转到应用程序属性
support the configuration files for
支持以下配置文件
spring boot we see here just one
春天的靴子，我们在这里只看到一个
property which is strike true
属实的财产
so it's a deprecated property IntelliJ
所以这是一个已弃用的属性IntelliJ
wants us about this
希望我们对此
there's also quick fix to replace it
也有快速的解决方法来替换它
with any new property which is the
与任何新的财产是
deprecation replacement and one nice new
弃用更换和一个不错的新
thing is when you open the documentation
事情是当您打开文档时
for that configuration property now you
对于该配置属性，现在您
can also click on the replacement named
也可以单击名为
property and see the documentation for
属性，请参阅有关的文档
the new replacement configure without
新的替代配置没有
having to insert it into your
必须将其插入您的
application of properties there have
应用属性那里有
been a couple of fixes for application
修复了一些应用程序
properties and application Yama's
属性和应用Yama's
support in general we improve this port
一般而言，我们的支持会改进此端口
for some a bit more exotic ways of
对于一些更奇特的方式
noting the configuration keys
注意配置键
Springwood allows a variety of notations
Springwood允许使用多种符号
for example lowercase mixture and stuff
例如小写的混合和东西
like that we are much better now in
这样我们现在好多了
supporting a bit more exotic variations
支持更多异国情调的变化
of debt when you use automatic and
使用自动和
IntelliJ IDEA which can be configured in
可以在以下位置配置的IntelliJ IDEA
the compiler settings make project
编译器设置使项目
automatically to support small projects
自动支持小型项目
which create a local spring metadata
创建本地spring元数据
using the add configuration properties
使用添加配置属性
correctly there was a problem with that
正确地有一个问题
before this has been fixed now okay
在此之前解决现在好了
that's all we have to show about spring
这就是我们要展示的关于春天的一切
boot and latest release and I am going
引导和最新版本，我要去
to switch now to a different project for
现在切换到其他项目
the other stuff and we are going to
其他的东西，我们将要
start with spring caching so Stefan what
从春季缓存开始，所以斯特凡
is spring caching about so the caching
是春天缓存，所以缓存
you're abstraction in Spring Framework
你是Spring Framework中的抽象
is no it's not new really it's been
不，这不是新的，真的
there for a while and we improved the
在那里一段时间，我们改善了
support in the in the latest for sort of
在最新的支持中
X line so basically the caching
X线所以基本上是缓存
infrastructure allows you
基础架构可以让您
to tag methods beat methods as to
标记方法击败方法
include a cash aspect and when you do so
包括现金方面，当您这样做时
spring will automatically check if you
春天会自动检查您是否
value the value that's been computed by
值计算的值
the method has already been cashed
该方法已经兑现
beforehand so again maybe you can open a
事先再说一次，也许你可以打开一个
class which has some cache of an
具有一些缓存的类
annotation on it so that we can get that
对其进行注释，以便我们可以获取
one so if we look at this one which is a
因此，如果我们看一下这是一个
bad example because it's only on an
不好的例子，因为它只在
interface but we will we'll discuss that
界面，但我们将讨论
in a minute so you have this built into
一分钟后，您就可以将其内置
a journalist that returns a list of
返回以下内容的新闻记者
integer and it takes started and
整数，它开始并
parameter if you if you add this
如果您添加此参数
annotation on your bin methods the
bin方法上的注释
default behavior is to computer key
默认行为是计算机密钥
based on the start and the end value and
根据开始和结束值，以及
whenever you invoke that method in your
每当您在自己的方法中调用该方法
code and there is a cash aspect which
代码，并且有一个现金方面
will first check if that key is
将首先检查该密钥是否为
available in the in the cache name
在缓存名称中可用
Micah's name if that's the case the
米卡的名字，如果是这样的话
method will not even be invoked so
方法甚至不会被调用，所以
you'll get the you get the entry in the
你会得到你得到的条目
cache directly if it isn't we will
如果不是，直接缓存
invoke the method as usual and before
和往常一样调用该方法
returning the value to the caller we
返回值给调用者我们
will also get the cache so that next
还将获取缓存，以便下一步
call with the stable start and end
用稳定的开始和结束进行呼叫
parameter have a chance to eat the cache
参数有机会吃掉缓存
in step okay thanks the phone for that
一步步好，谢谢手机
introduction to spring caching so as you
弹簧缓存简介
said we have the casual annotation here
说我们这里有随意的注解
on the interface and just warning from
在界面上，只是警告
IntelliJ IDEA that's a new inspection
IntelliJ IDEA是一项新检查
why does spring not recommend to enter
为什么春天不建议进入
annotate the interface yes so yeah
注释界面是的，是的
before I reply to that I think that this
在我回复之前，我认为这是
is new annotate these new inspections
是新注释这些新检查
are really great because it's a way for
真的很棒，因为这是
us to promote some best practices VRD
我们推广VRD的一些最佳做法
IDE so the tools that you're using to
IDE，因此您使用的工具
code give you immediate feedback about
代码为您提供有关以下内容的即时反馈
things you're doing and also advice on
您正在做的事情以及建议
how to design your components
如何设计您的组件
this particular case the reason why
这种特殊情况的原因
we've added this inspection is because
我们添加此检查是因为
you shouldn't put implementation details
你不应该把实施细节
only interface this is really an
唯一的界面，这真的是
implementation detail and you may have
实施细节，您可能会有
an implementation of this of this
这个的实现
service that does not require cashing a
不需要兑现的服务
note for whatever reason if you put them
不论出于何种原因请注意
on the interface however there is really
在界面上，但是实际上
no way to disable that and it's an
没有办法禁用它，这是一个
implementation detail that becomes the
实施细节成为
default okay right so let's follow the
默认好吧，所以让我们按照
advice of the inspection and do year of
检查的建议，并在
best practices disabling this annotation
禁用此注释的最佳实践
on the interface and let's have a look
在界面上，让我们看一下
at the actual implementation here so we
在这里的实际实施中，所以我们
have this server Co which implements our
有这个实现我们的服务器
caching service and the method built
缓存服务及其构建方法
integer lists so now I'm putting the
整数列表，所以现在我将
Kerbal annotation on the implementation
关于实现的喀尔巴鄂注释
just like the inspection told us but
就像检查告诉我们的一样，
just the problem here and IntelliJ wants
只是这里的问题，IntelliJ想要
us that we should provide a cache name
我们应该提供一个缓存名称
which is basically like a key or hash
基本上就像是键或哈希
key to store results from the caching
存储缓存结果的关键
and for spring to look it up and return
春天来了，然后返回
the test results instead of invocation
测试结果而不是调用
so this is again this is again how di D
所以这又是这又如何
can really help us and really help you
可以真正帮助我们，也可以真正帮助您
to figure out about the feature that has
弄清楚具有的功能
evolved over time initially when the the
最初随着时间的流逝而发展
caching abstraction was introduced the
引入了缓存抽象
the cache name so did the name of the
缓存名称也是如此
cache that should be used for that
缓存应该用于
particular method was a mandatory
特定方法是强制性的
attribute so whenever you use cashable
属性，以便每当您使用Cashable时
and if you didn't provide a cache name
如果您没有提供缓存名称
attribute your code would not compile so
属性您的代码将无法编译，因此
it was really easy for you to realize
您真的很容易意识到
that something was wrong in the meantime
在此期间出了点问题
the community asked us to improve the
社区要求我们改善
current support and you can you can
当前的支持，你可以
basically see that at class level there
基本上在课堂上看到
was discussion figure notation so one of
是讨论图形符号，所以其中之一
the thing that the community asked us to
社区要求我们做的事情
improve
提高
was a way to externalize the the name of
是外在化名称的一种方式
the cache to use for one you can
您可以使用的缓存
put cash configured class level now it's
现在将现金配置为课程级别
been a while but if you do so any cash
已经有一段时间了，但如果您这样做的话，任何现金
method on that class will use the
该类上的方法将使用
caching service cache so you don't have
缓存服务缓存，因此您没有
to repeat that value over and over again
一遍又一遍地重复该值
next which is not on this on this code
下一个不在此代码上
there isn't an extra attribute that
没有一个额外的属性
we've introduced called cache resolver
我们介绍了所谓的缓存解析器
and calf is over is the name of a bean
小牛结束了是豆的名字
just like the system cache manager
就像系统缓存管理器一样
attribute there and if you specify it we
属性在那里，如果您指定它，我们
will invoke the bean so the calf is over
将调用bean，以便小牛结束
implementation and you'll have a chance
实施，您将有机会
to compute the cache name to use at
计算要在以下位置使用的缓存名称
runtime so long story short there is
长话短说
many ways to specify the cache name now
现在有很多方法可以指定缓存名称
and the attribute can't be on data
并且该属性不能在数据上
anymore
不再
so we needed a way to warn you about hey
所以我们需要一种警告您的方法
this this class has no name whatsoever
这个班没有名字
are you sure that's really what you want
您确定这就是您想要的吗
so it's really great that the idea gives
所以这个主意确实很棒
support for that okay it's the fun so we
支持那好吧，这很有趣，所以我们
are going to uncomment the class level
要取消对班级的评论
cache config notation here which does
在这里缓存配置符号
define the cache names and immediately
定义缓存名称并立即
the inspection goes away just as
检查就消失了
expected so we have a couple of
期望如此，我们有几个
attributes here like the cache manager
这里的属性，例如缓存管理器
key key generator and those true is off
密钥生成器，并且那些真值是关闭的
to custom implementation beans you can
自定义实现bean，您可以
provide for teespring caching to pickup
提供teespring缓存以备取用
and of course we have Auto completion
当然我们有自动完成
here as usually you can control click
通常可以在这里控制点击
here to go there and go back to the
这里去那里，然后回到
config not Tory service again for a
配置不再次提供Tory服务
minute let's just remove the cache names
分钟，我们只删除缓存名称
attribute from the class level and put
类级别的属性并放入
it on this method here and what I'm
它在这里和我的这种方法
going to do now is introduce another
现在要做的是介绍另一个
method just for demonstration purposes
仅用于演示目的的方法
should probably have the same return
应该有相同的回报
type and just return
输入并返回
tamo value here and at the same cashable
此处的tamo价值和可兑现的相同价值
annotation on this method as well so we
该方法的注释也是如此，所以我们
have no two methods which used the same
没有两个使用相同方法的方法
cache name and you could see that
缓存名称，您会看到
IntelliJ immediately adds a new gutter
IntelliJ立即添加新的装订线
icon here which allows you to go to
此处的图标，可让您转到
other cache of the annotations which use
使用该注释的其他缓存
the same cache name so when i duplicate
相同的缓存名称，所以当我重复时
this once again give it a second name I
再次给它起个名字我
can actually get a list of all the
可以实际得到所有
methods annotated with cacheable using
使用cacheable注释的方法
the same cache name and I can quickly
相同的缓存名称，我可以快速
navigate between them to make sure that
在他们之间导航以确保
they actually should be in the same rule
他们实际上应该遵循相同的规则
okay that's about in navigation
好的，这就是导航
focusable and just a quick note you can
重点突出，只需快速注释一下即可
also provide your own meta annotation of
还提供您自己的元注释
cashable so you can add maybe some
可兑现的，所以您可以添加一些
custom attributes there or use allies
在那里自定义属性或使用盟友
for to redefine the existing attributes
用于重新定义现有属性
all these four we have here will also
我们在这里拥有的所有这四个
work for your custom meta a patient as
为您的自定义元患者工作
well
好
so let's jump into the next topic which
所以我们跳到下一个主题
is spring al or just spell springy
是春季，还是拼写有弹性
Ellison expression language provided by
Ellison表达语言提供者
the spring framework and which is used
弹簧框架和使用
throughout all these spring sub projects
在所有这些春季子项目中
and it allows you to define a runtime
它允许您定义运行时
conditions or evaluations at various
各种条件或评估
points so we can see that this condition
点，所以我们可以看到这种情况
attribute here has some slightly
这里的属性略有
different background color and this
不同的背景颜色和这个
sends us to the fact that here we find a
让我们发现，在这里我们找到了一个
spell expression which actually defines
实际定义的拼写表达
the condition that should be evaluated
应该评估的条件
at runtime and one thing that we
在运行时，我们要做的一件事
improved a lot now is that we use
现在改善了很多，我们使用
context dependent variables we can use
我们可以使用的上下文相关变量
context dependent variables so for
因此上下文相关变量
example the schedule annotation knows
时间表注释知道的示例
about the parameters we have here on
关于我们这里的参数
this method so I can actually control
这样我就可以实际控制
click here and go to the parameter which
单击此处并转到参数
is automatically resolved in this spell
在这个咒语中自动解决
expression this of course means that we
表达这当然意味着我们
have Auto completion for the parameters
有自动完成的参数
here as well Stefan wants to add some
Stefan也想在这里添加一些
bit here so if you look if you look at
咬一下这里，如果你看的话
the if you open it the condition Javadoc
如果您将其打开，则条件为Javadoc
he opened the puppet maybe to show to
他打开了木偶，也许要向
the audience here um if you scroll a bit
这里的观众，如果您滚动一下
you will see that this this Javadoc is
您会看到这个Javadoc是
actually quite extensive explaining you
实际上相当广泛的解释你
what the context for this particular
这个特定的背景是什么
spring expression language default is so
春季表达语言默认为
you can see that you can access to the
您会看到您可以访问
method you can access to the target
您可以访问目标的方法
which is the target instance you can
这是目标实例
access to the caches that are going to
访问将要访问的缓存
be used for that matter and the the root
用于那个问题和根本
the root context actually changes from
根上下文实际上从
one expression support to the other we
一种表达支持另一种表达
will see that in a minute
一会儿就会看到
so this is really great that we have a
所以这真的很棒，我们有一个
to completion support for
完成对
spell now because that way you get
现在拼写，因为这样您就可以
actually assistance of what we support
实际上是我们所支持的协助
the kind of viable that you can use in
您可以在其中使用的可行性
your spell expression right
你的咒语表达正确
Stephan just mentioned the
斯蒂芬刚才提到
context-dependent route variables or
上下文相关的路由变量或
route objects and as you can see the
路由对象，如您所见
route object is actually known here and
实际上在这里知道路由对象，并且
that to the prototype which will be used
到将要使用的原型
at run time by spring and of course we
在春季运行时，当然我们
can access all the properties from that
可以从中访问所有属性
object as well so that's a very nice way
对象，所以这是一个非常好的方法
to just get very nice context dependent
只是获得非常好的上下文相关
assistance completion navigation in all
全部协助完成导航
these expression places this also works
这些表达方式也可以
small in spring security so for spring
春季安全性较小，因此春季
security we have various annotations
安全我们有各种注释
where we support spell as well let's
我们也支持咒语
just quickly jump to one very simple
很快就跳到一个非常简单的
sample here are using the ad
这里的示例正在使用广告
pre-authorized annotation and as you can
预先授权的注释
see there is a has roll method which is
看到有一个has roll方法
called here and again this is yield
一遍又一遍地叫这是产量
object which is provided by spring
弹簧提供的物体
security at runtime for the spell
咒语在运行时的安全性
context and we have again Auto
上下文，我们又有了Auto
completion here for all the methods for
在这里完成所有方法
example we have here and you know it's
例如我们在这里，你知道它是
just a nice way to make sure you don't
只是确保您不会的好方法
miss type or miss any of key noise
错过类型或错过任何关键噪音
features which are actually available in
实际可用的功能
this aspera context of course you can
您当然可以在这种aspera环境中
use quick documentation on any of the
在任何
method calls but the nice new thing is
方法调用，但是好的新事物是
that we edit and spell language support
我们编辑和拼写语言支持
is now we show we support also the show
现在我们展示我们也支持展示
parameter info
参数信息
shortcut so when I use command P I can
快捷方式，所以当我使用命令PI时可以
actually see the parameters just method
实际看到参数只是方法
has to offer let's just use one with a
必须提供让我们只使用一个
bit more parameters and you can just use
多一些参数，您可以使用
it as you know it from Java or any other
正如您从Java或其他任何工具中了解的那样
programming languages
编程语言
which has this feature another nice
具有这个功能的另一个好地方
thing which was improved mess-free for
改善的东西没有混乱
the sport in 2016 or two is improved
2016或两项运动得到改善
auto completion so we have all the
自动完成，所以我们拥有所有
keywords here we have very nice auto
这里的关键字，我们有很好的自动
completion for example for tu type
例如tu类型的完成
reference so I just type T and tap and
参考，所以我只输入T然后点按
it will automatically switch to the
它将自动切换到
class name so I can provide the class
课程名称，以便我提供课程
name here just anything and of course
在这里命名任何东西，当然
you can navigate to the class again use
您可以再次导航到该类
the Javadoc feature and this even works
Javadoc功能，甚至可以使用
for renaming so when you refer to one
重命名，所以当您提到一个
class in your project and you rename
项目中的课程，然后重命名
that class all these references will be
该类所有这些引用将是
updated as you would expect from
如您期望的那样进行了更新
IntelliJ of course Auto completion is
IntelliJ当然是自动完成
also improved when you type special
当您键入特殊字符时也有所改善
characters so when you type this sign it
字符，所以当您键入此符号时
will automatically pop up the auto
会自动弹出自动
completion menu so you can continue
完成菜单，以便您可以继续
typing here the same is true for the @
在这里输入@同样适用
sign and on top of that there have been
标志，最重要的是
many many dozens of fixes to the parsing
解析的很多很多修复
and evaluation of these expressions so
对这些表达式进行评估
for example we support inline maps
例如，我们支持嵌入式地图
notation this is something where you can
表示法，您可以在这里
put a key with a value just inside your
将一个带有值的键放在您的内部
spell expression and it will create a
拼写表达，它将创建一个
map on the fly at this point another
即时地图上的另一个
thing which is know properly passed our
正确知道的事情通过了我们
hexadecimal numbers they start with o
以o开头的十六进制数
weeks and I actually learned that that
个星期，我实际上了解到
the key verse are actually case
关键经文实际上是个案
insensitive so if you prefer to write
不敏感，所以如果您喜欢写
okay strew instead of lowercase true
好吧，散布而不是小写true
that's not properly passed as well there
那里还没有正确通过
have been literally dozens of fixes so
实际上已经修复了数十个，
if your spell expression maybe had some
如果你的咒语表达可能有一些
problems before give it a try
尝试之前的问题
I hope it's fixed but another big new
我希望它已修复，但又是一个新的重大改进
feature in the spell language support is
拼写语言支持中的功能是
no we have a dedicated to color settings
不，我们有专门的颜色设置
page for dispel language so if for
消除语言页面，因此
example you don't like the default color
例如，您不喜欢默认颜色
scheme we can just for example change
我们可以例如更改方案
the keyword highlighting and choose a
关键字突出显示并选择一个
bit different color like this and you
像这样和你有点不同的颜色
can see it in the preview the colors
可以在预览中看到它的颜色
picked up and this effects now really
捡起来，这种影响现在真的
only dispel language previously it was
以前只是消除语言
using the same settings as a JSP
使用与JSP相同的设置
expression language but because springy
表达语言，但因为有弹性
our language has so many more features
我们的语言还有很多功能
than 2jc a language that we finally
比2jc的语言，我们终于
added a dedicated settings page just for
添加了专门的设置页面
that language so that's all from spell
该语言，这全是拼写
for me but Stephane once at a bit yeah
对我来说，但斯蒂芬（Stephane）有点过
if you could if you could open that and
如果可以，请打开
then again I have an advice for you guys
再说一遍，我对你们有个建议
is to trigger the background color for
触发背景色
the spell expression so if you do that
咒语表达，所以如果你这样做
you see that in a minute when yawn
你在打哈欠的一分钟内看到
my name is this every spell expression
我叫这个咒语
in your code will be we have a dedicated
在您的代码中，我们将专门
background color the nice thing about
背景色的妙处
that is it IntelliJ IDEA will
就是IntelliJ IDEA
automatically recognizes the places
自动识别地点
where you can actually use an expression
您可以实际使用表达式的地方
so if you happen to try a new feature of
因此，如果您碰巧尝试了一项新功能，
the framework and you you open this
框架，您打开它
attribute you don't know about and if
您不知道的属性以及是否
you start typing you will immediately
您开始打字，您将立即
see one that it's a spell expression and
看到这是一个咒语表达，
two what what kind of features you can
两个你可以拥有什么样的功能
use with it so it's really
使用它，所以它真的
assistance network namely ID for that
协助网络，即该ID
stuff it's really great right yeah
东西真的很棒，是的
that's a nice tip from Stefan by the way
顺便说一句，这是斯特凡的一个不错的提示
you can use the language injection
您可以使用语言注入
feature in IntelliJ IDEA make sure the
IntelliJ IDEA中的功能确保
billion is enabled it allows you to
启用十亿美元
inject custom languages in any of the
以任何一种方式注入自定义语言
supported places one of those places are
支持的地方这些地方之一是
string literals so for example if I add
字符串文字，例如，如果我添加
a custom attribute in my meta annotation
我的元注释中的自定义属性
which should be spell enabled I can just
应该启用拼写，我可以
use all enter and use the inject
使用所有输入并使用注入
language reference feature to make
语言参考功能
IntelliJ know that this attribute is
IntelliJ知道此属性是
actually a spell language expression and
实际上是一种拼写语言表达，
you will receive all these spell
您将收到所有这些咒语
highlighting and auto-completion
突出显示和自动完成
in those places as well so that's a nice
在那些地方也是如此，这是一个很好的
thing if you add some custom stuff in
如果您在其中添加一些自定义内容
annotations or in XML that's also
注释或XML
supported okay so much about ta
太支持了
springier support next topic spring core
springier支持下一个主题spring core
so the spring framework itself one thing
所以Spring框架本身是一回事
improved a lot is the overall
整体改善很多
performance when you have multiple
有多个时的性能
projects open simultaneously the overall
项目同时开放
highlighting performance will just be
突出表现只是
much better now and let's go into a
现在好多了，让我们进入
sample configuration which will showcase
样本配置将展示
a new inspection we edit in the latest
我们最近编辑的新检查
release which is about outer wiring and
释放有关外部接线和
you can see that in this configuration
您可以看到在此配置中
class let's just focus on this auto
上课让我们专注于这个自动
wired field here there's a new
有线领域这里有一个新的
inspection which actually highlights the
检查实际上突出了
outer wire annotation itself stating
外线注解本身说明
that field injection is not recommended
不建议现场注入
Stephan can you tell us a bit more about
斯蒂芬你能告诉我们更多有关
this please
这个请
of course I can so the auto irony field
我当然可以这样，汽车讽刺领域
has been like something we discourage
就像我们不鼓励的事情
for quite some time now we even have one
在相当长的一段时间里，我们甚至有一个
of our team member writing a blog post
团队成员撰写博客文章的过程
years ago about it the reason why we
多年前关于它的原因
don't recommend it is because there is a
不建议是因为有一个
lifecycle issue attached to it if for
如果附加了生命周期问题
instance since it's a field you expect
实例，因为它是您期望的字段
that field we are available in the
该字段可以在
constructor right so if you Auto Y or a
正确的构造函数，所以如果您使用Auto Y或
field like that and you want to access
这样的字段，您想访问
it in the constructor you'll get a new
在构造函数中，您将获得一个新的
printer exception the reason why is to
打印机异常的原因是
be able to set the field using
能够使用设置字段
reflection we actually need a beam
反射我们实际上需要光束
instance to be able to do so so the
实例能够做到这一点
first thing that we'll do is actually
我们要做的第一件事实际上是
create the instance of the beam and
创建梁的实例并
right after using reflection set the
使用反射后立即设置
value of the field itself so it's really
字段本身的价值，所以它真的
a weird life cycle it's it's really not
怪异的生命周期，真的不是
something that you would expect to work
您希望工作的东西
like that and also we have added
这样，我们还添加了
constructor injection on across the
构造函数注入
board in photo 3 so you can use
照片3中的画板，因此您可以使用
constructor injection in configuration
配置中的构造函数注入
classes now so there's really no reason
现在上课，所以真的没有理由
to no reason to use chin rejection on on
没有理由在下巴上使用下巴剔除
production code in tests personally I
我亲自测试中的生产代码
use still injection quite a lot because
使用静注很多，因为
there isn't there is there isn't really
那里没有那里真的没有
this issue of having a constructor in
这个有一个构造函数的问题
the test so this is this is easier on
测试，所以这更容易
the eye to do it in test and IntelliJ
在测试和IntelliJ中做到这一点
won't warn you in test either right so
也不会在测试中警告您，所以
we have this warning here from IntelliJ
我们在这里收到来自IntelliJ的警告
and of course the first step you do when
当然，您要做的第一步是
you see a warning is to hit alt enter to
您看到警告是按alt输入
see if there is a quick fix and of
看看是否有快速解决方案和
course there is one which is to change
当然有一个是要改变的
that auto wired on the field itself to
自动将现场连线到
constructor injection just like Stephan
像Stephan一样的构造函数注入
explained so when I invoke this the auto
解释了，所以当我调用这个自动
wired annotation will be moved to the
有线注释将移至
constructor and the field will be set in
构造函数，该字段将设置在
the constructor and one thing you can do
构造函数和您可以做的一件事
when you have only one constructor in
当您只有一个构造函数时
your configuration classes actually also
您的配置类实际上也
to remove the auto wired annotation from
从中删除自动有线注释
the constructor itself so your code
构造函数本身，所以您的代码
looks a bit less spring injected than
看起来比注入的弹簧少
before
之前
okay another topic about Auto wiring is
好吧，关于自动接线的另一个话题是
support for generics so we have here
支持泛型，所以我们在这里
another configuration which requires two
另一种配置需要两个
parameters in the construction for auto
汽车构造中的参数
wiring again the auto wired annotation
重新连线自动连线注解
is not mandatory here anymore we only
在这里不再是强制性的，我们只
have one constructor so I have this
有一个构造函数，所以我有这个
repository interface which receives type
接收类型的存储库接口
parameter and I have two types here one
参数，这里有两种类型
employee one Department and both are
员工一个部门，都
defined as member variables in this
在此定义为成员变量
configuration the beans are provided in
Bean所提供的配置
the same configuration class just for
相同的配置类
demonstration purposes and as you can
示范目的
see there are no tool out of wire
看到没有电线的工具
dependencies cutter icons here and
这里的依赖切割器图标和
IntelliJ will now correctly resolve
IntelliJ现在可以正确解析
according to the generic type which is
根据通用类型是
marked as the type parameter of the
标记为
repository here so the employee
在这里存储，以便员工
repository which I can navigate using
我可以使用浏览的存储库
this icon will be correctly resolved
此图标将被正确解析
when I go back from the department
当我从部门回来时
repository bean definition to the places
仓库bean定义到地方
where it is used as an auto Wyatt
用作自动悦悦的地方
candidate it will not show me okay
候选人不会告诉我好吗
just about Khepera needs but the other
差不多是Khepera的需要，但另一个
way around it works
解决方法
sorry that's of course demonstrations
抱歉，那当然是示范
okay another topic our event listeners
好的，我们的事件监听器还有一个话题
and those have been supported in
那些在
previous version of IntelliJ already we
以前的IntelliJ版本
improve the support a bit for custom
改进对自定义的支持
meta annotations for event listeners so
事件侦听器的元注释，因此
here I have my custom event listener
这是我的自定义事件监听器
annotation which inherits from T
继承自T的注释
original spring event listener
原始的春季事件监听器
annotation and when I go to
注释，当我去
the place where it's actually used I use
我实际使用过的地方
the eventlistener notation here again we
这里再次使用事件监听器符号
have despair support we can see this
有绝望的支持，我们可以看到这个
very nicely using the custom nice on the
非常好使用
eye back roncada we said before and when
回望龙卡达，我们之前和时间
I use my custom event listener
我使用我的自定义事件监听器
annotation where I redefined D condition
我重新定义D条件的注释
attribute to be a different name you can
属性可以是其他名称
see these support works just the same as
看到这些支持工作与
in these standard spring annotations so
在这些标准的弹簧注释中
let's go back quickly to the main
让我们快速回到主要
configuration we have apparently some
配置我们显然有一些
problem here in the auto wiring process
自动接线过程中的问题
because there are multiple beans which
因为有多个豆子
would match the candidates and this is
将匹配候选人，这是
of course done intentionally for
当然是故意为
demonstration purposes so when I try to
示范目的，所以当我尝试
run this main configuration the spring
在春季运行此主要配置
context will of course fail to start up
上下文当然不会启动
because there's an unsatisfied
因为有一个不满意的
dependency here and the nice thing is
依赖在这里，好东西是
now in these consult X we will detect
现在在这些X中，我们将检测到
some specific error messages which are
一些特定的错误消息是
provided by the spring framework for
由spring框架提供
example error creating bean with name
使用名称创建bean的示例错误
and as soon as we find those error
一旦发现这些错误
messages in the run console we will pass
运行控制台中的消息，我们将通过
them and allow you to actually control
他们，让你实际控制
click here and go to the corresponding
单击此处并转到相应的
bean because IntelliJ knows where your
bean，因为IntelliJ知道您的位置
beans are and how they are named so
豆是什么以及它们如何命名
that's a nice way when your application
这是当您的应用程序的好方法
fails to start after some changes to
进行一些更改后无法启动
quickly go to the places where something
赶快去一些地方
is apparently warm and most probably
显然很温暖，很可能
IntelliJ would also have the
IntelliJ也将具有
corresponding inspection for you and
为您和您进行相应的检查
help you fixing it
帮助您修复它
yeah I was about to say that Yun and I
是的，我正要说允和我
had a nice chat yesterday preparing the
昨天准备了一个愉快的聊天
webinar and we were looking at some of
网络研讨会，我们正在研究一些
the some of the error message that
一些错误消息
Spring Framework in Springwood are
Springwood中的Spring Framework是
producing and we already found together
生产，我们已经发现在一起
a few new inspections that could be
一些新的检查可能是
added to IntelliJ IDE so maybe you will
已添加到IntelliJ IDE，所以也许您会
find some yourself and feel free to
找到自己，随时随地
report that to you track and it might be
报告给您跟踪，可能是
added in in the future release
在将来的版本中添加
intelligent right another common error
智慧权是另一个常见错误
is the message could not Auto wire beam
是消息无法自动线束
and that will be passed as well just the
那也将通过
same way as we had for the error
与我们对错误的处理方式相同
creating beam okay a quick excursion to
可以快速创建光束
somewhat more special or not so commonly
有点特殊或不是那么普遍
used topic which is improved support for
已使用的主题，对的改进
the spring dot factories fire and Stefan
春季点工厂大火和斯蒂芬
can tell us a bit more what key spring
可以告诉我们更多关键弹簧
to factorize files are about so this is
使文件分解的原因是
a generic SPI from Spring Framework that
来自Spring Framework的通用SPI
allows you to load implementation of a
允许您加载一个
certain interface or load certain
某些接口或某些负载
components easily so we use that
组件很容易，所以我们使用
internally for instance in spring
内部例如春季
framework to allow you to register an
允许您注册一个框架
application listener as part of a jar
应用侦听器作为jar的一部分
and make sure that application listener
并确保该应用程序监听器
will be invoked automatically even
甚至会被自动调用
though you did not register it on the
尽管您没有在
contacts yourself so basically if you
基本上就是这样联系自己
have an application listener and you
有一个应用程序监听器，您
want to make sure it's going to be
想要确保它将会是
invoked you create a spring factories at
调用您在创建弹簧工厂
a certain place and you register your
某个地方，你注册你的
implementation in this case my
在这种情况下我的实现
application listener in that file Spring
该文件中的应用程序侦听器Spring
Framework will scan all spring factories
框架将扫描所有春季工厂
file from the classpath and will
文件从类路径，将
automatically register components this
自动注册组件
is how spring boot is spring boot
春天的靴子是怎样的
auto-configuration is working by the way
自动配置顺便说一句
so if you want to create your own Auto
因此，如果您要创建自己的自动
configuration you need to tell spring
你需要告诉弹簧的配置
boot to actually invoke it on startup if
引导以在启动时实际调用它
there are beans that
有些豆子
to be created and the way you do this in
被创建以及您在其中进行的方式
Springwood is to register your total
Springwood要注册您的总数
configuration fully qualified name using
使用配置全限定名
a given key so in this case if we look
给定的键，在这种情况下，如果我们看
at this new icon next to the to the
在该图标旁边的
class and we click on it we'll actually
类，然后单击它，我们实际上
navigate to the spring factories define
导航到弹簧工厂定义
on that module there you can find the
在该模块上，您可以找到
key so in this case this is the summer
关键，在这种情况下，这是夏天
key and spring framework to register
要注册的关键和春季框架
listeners and you'll see the fully
听众，您将看到完整的
qualified name of the class so yang can
该类的合格名称，因此yang可以
maybe show us no more inspections about
也许不告诉我们更多关于
that yes of course you can control click
是的，您当然可以控制点击
here again to go back to the actual
这里再次回到实际
class using the qualified name of course
使用课程的合格名称的课程
we factoring works again here
我们在这里再次进行保理工作
and IntelliJ also knows about some
IntelliJ也知道一些
default keys so the other one for
默认键，所以另一个
example which is available in the spring
春季可用的示例
core framework is the application
核心框架是应用程序
context initializer so that's another
上下文初始化器，这是另一个
predefined key there are others for
预定义键还有其他用于
spring good ones Stefan just mentioned
春天的好朋友斯蒂芬刚才提到
they will be available automatically
他们将自动可用
depending on the availability of spring
取决于弹簧的可用性
libraries in your project
您项目中的库
ok so much about these spring factory
这些弹簧工厂很好
support let's jump into spring MVC no so
支持让我们跳入Spring MVC吧
here we have a very basic spring MVC
这里我们有一个非常基本的spring MVC
controller with two requests mappings
具有两个请求映射的控制器
and we have one here just called perform
我们这里有一个叫做表演
and that's what I call old school
那就是我所说的老派
because it's using a JSP page for the
因为它使用的是JSP页面
view so this I can here as always been
查看，因此我可以像往常一样在这里
existing it allows you to navigate to
现有，它允许您导航到
the related view or to the related views
相关视图或相关视图
which are used in just request mapping
仅在请求映射中使用
you can also use control click here on
您也可以使用控制点击这里
the view name in the constructor of the
的构造函数中的视图名称
model and view to navigate to the
模型和视图以导航到
resolve JSP page we always support at
解决我们一直支持的JSP页面
resolving attributes which are provided
解决提供的属性
within
内
the request mapping method so we can
请求映射方法，以便我们可以
actually see that this attribute we put
实际上看到我们把这个属性
into the model and view map here
进入模型并在此处查看地图
available in our JSP elo context I can
在我们的JSP elo上下文中可用
control click here and go to the actual
控制单击此处，转到实际
definition of that variable
该变量的定义
this noir works also in velocity and
这个黑色也可以在速度和
free marker so in the second request
免费标记，因此在第二个请求中
mapping which is a bit more up-to-date
映射是最新的
we use free marker again you can control
我们再次使用免费标记，您可以控制
click here or use the gutter icon to
单击此处或使用装订线图标进行操作
navigate to the related views my
导航到我的相关视图
preferred way actually of navigating to
实际导航到的首选方式
that is using the navigate related
使用导航相关
symbol shortcut which is a generic
通用的符号快捷方式
shortcut to navigate to anything that is
导航到任何内容的快捷方式
somehow related to the current
与当前有关
invocation context so this shortcut
调用上下文，因此此快捷方式
actually works in a number of places
实际上在许多地方都可以使用
also for spring beans for example to
也用于春豆
quickly show you for example related out
快速向您展示相关的例子
of beans of the wire and cut into
线豆切成
candidates and stuff like that so when I
候选人之类的东西，所以当我
do that it will actually propose me the
这样做实际上会向我提出建议
corresponding free mark of you and now
您和现在的相应免费标记
we also support resolving those
我们也支持解决这些问题
attributes in free marker and velocity a
自由标记和速度a中的属性
nice trick to see a bit more about this
看到更多关于这个的好技巧
attribute is actually to use the show
属性实际上是要使用show
quick definition shortcut ctrl shift E
快速定义快捷键ctrl shift E
and that actually shows you the
这实际上向您展示了
navigation target but without leaving
导航目标但没有离开
the current editor so you get a pop-up
当前的编辑器，因此您会弹出一个窗口
which shows you the same as if you would
它显示出与您将看到的相同的图像
navigate to the extra code spring and
导航到额外的代码spring和
the C's of protests received a number of
C的抗议收到了许多
fixes for the ad model attribute
修复广告模型属性
handling sorry and not a nice little
处理抱歉，不是一个好小东西
touch we added here is when you pull
我们在这里添加的触摸是当您拉动时
the method attribute here to limited tea
这里的方法属性是有限的茶
request mapping to certain a HTTP
请求映射到某些HTTP
methods this is always shown in the
方法总是显示在
spring MVC to Lenore so when I list the
春天的MVC到Lenore，所以当我列出
request mappings here you can clearly
在这里请求映射，您可以清楚地看到
see the get request mapping here in the
请参阅此处的获取请求映射
brackets and they are also in the quick
括号，它们也很快
dock and this is also shown more in the
停靠，这也显示在
go-to symbol navigation dialog so when I
转到符号导航对话框，所以当我
use command alt shift m4 go to symbol
使用命令alt shift m4转到符号
and when I type a forward slash I can
当我输入正斜杠时，我可以
see all the register to request mappings
查看所有注册请求映射
in my project and now we request methods
在我的项目中，现在我们请求方法
will also be shown in this navigation
也将在此导航中显示
pop-up so if you have multiple requests
弹出，因此如果您有多个请求
mappings was the same path but using
映射是相同的路径，但使用
different HTTP methods it's more much
不同的HTTP方法
easier to distinguish them in this form
以这种形式更容易区分它们
so that's about it for spring MVC and
这就是Spring MVC的相关内容，
actually we are finished with showing
实际上我们已经完成了展示
all the new stuff or updated stuff we
所有新的东西或我们更新的东西
edit in 20 in 16.2 so naturally Before
在16.2中自然编辑20
we jump into Q &amp; A we would like to give
我们跳入问答环节
you a short update on the plans for 2016
您2016年计划的简短更新
door 3 which will be released later and
3号门，稍后将释放
fall this year so again let's start with
今年秋天，让我们再次开始
spring boot spring boot one word for
弹簧靴弹簧靴
support has a new much extended support
支持有了新的扩展支持
for testing as Stefan told us in the
如Stefan在
beginning so we are going to support all
开始，所以我们将支持所有
the new spring boot testing annotations
新的Spring Boot测试注释
so you been resolving and stuff like
所以你一直在解决
that will work just like in the plain
就像在平原上一样
spring core context configuration setups
Spring核心上下文配置设置
the next and probably biggest topic is
下一个也是最大的话题是
to make the spring and the C support
使弹簧和C支撑
work for spring boot applications so
适用于春季启动应用程序
that you can
你能行
enjoy the same level of support for
享有同等水平的支持
example navigating to request mappings
导航到请求映射的示例
resolving for model attributes as we
解决我们的模型属性
just saw as well for spring food
刚看到春天的食物
applications you might have heard of
您可能听说过的应用程序
Kotlin the JVM programming language
Kotlin JVM编程语言
which is quite new it was just released
这是很新的，它刚刚发布
this year the final one not all released
今年的最后一个不是全部发布
and it has been received very well in
而且在
the community and actually is bringing
社区，实际上正在带来
both guys really seem to love it so when
两个人似乎都喜欢它，所以当
you go to start of spring i/o you can
你去春天开始，我可以
actually create a quadlin spring boot
实际上创建一个四边形弹簧靴
template application and naturally we
模板应用程序，我们自然
want to extend the existing support for
想要扩展现有的支持
all the annotation all the highlight
所有注解所有突出显示
things and all the completion features
事物和所有完成功能
we already have for Java with any of
我们已经拥有Java与任何
those in frameworks to Kotlin as well so
那些在Kotlin框架内的人
right now
马上
support for spring using coughing code
使用咳嗽代码支持弹簧
is bundled with Indy cotton plug-in
与Indy棉插件捆绑在一起
itself which has some drawbacks but
本身有一些缺点，但
right now it's the only solution so we
现在这是唯一的解决方案，所以我们
are planning actually to extend the
正在实际计划扩展
existing support we have for Java step
我们对Java步骤的现有支持
by step to make it language agnostic so
逐步使其与语言无关
all the inspections navigation features
所有检查导航功能
will actually work with cutting code as
实际上将与切割代码一起使用
well
好
another big topic is supporting better
另一个大话题是支持更好
navigation for test contexts so right
正确导航测试上下文
now these ping to window and teespring
现在这些ping到window和teespring
facet and all the navigation for beans
方面和Bean的所有导航
just include the production contexts you
只包括您的生产环境
set up in the spring facet all the test
在春季进行所有测试
contexts are implicit using given
使用给定隐式上下文
annotations in your testing class you
在您的测试课程中的注释
can navigate to the config files but you
可以导航到配置文件，但是您
cannot actually see the resulting beans
实际上看不到生成的豆
for your test so that's one really
为了您的测试，这真的是
missing feature we are going to add in
我们要添加的缺失功能
the next week's the last but not least
下周是最后但并非最不重要的
we have already worked on some quite
我们已经做了一些相当
impressive performance improvements in
令人印象深刻的性能改进
the spring support meaning that any time
弹簧支撑意味着任何时候
you type something in any editor we will
您在任何编辑器中输入内容
have much less cache and validations in
具有更少的缓存和验证
our spring model we build ourselves to
我们的春天模型，我们建立自己
actually understand what your project is
真正了解您的项目是什么
doing so you will hopefully enjoy a much
这样做，您将有望享受很多
improved general performance not only
不仅改善了总体性能
with highlighting but in general the
突出显示，但总的来说
whole idea will be faster in the next
在接下来的整个想法会更快
release and the early access for 2016 to
发行版和2016年的抢先体验
tree should actually start later this
树实际上应该在以后开始
month and you all very much
一个月，你们都非常
invite to give it a try and please let
邀请尝试一下，请让
us know if either feedback and yeah vote
我们知道是否有反馈和赞成票
command on the existing issues or please
命令存在的问题或请
for new issues we are very happy to hear
对于新问题，我们很高兴听到
from you hear about your problems your
从您那里得知您的问题
wishes and yes that's it for now so time
希望是的，现在就这样
for Q&amp;A
进行问答
thank CNN Stefan for a very solid
感谢CNN斯蒂芬非常坚定
already let's see
已经让我们看看
questions we have in fact not many there
我们实际上没有很多问题
is a question from Thomas about an
是托马斯问的一个问题
option in run configuration similar to
运行配置中的选项类似于
one frame deactivation which we have for
一帧停用，我们有
for instance for ten Tomcat the question
例如十个Tomcat的问题
is whether we want to add it to the
是我们是否要将其添加到
Springwood launcher as well
以及Springwood发射器
Jung do you have anything to tell Molly
荣格，你有什么话要告诉莫莉
yes I take for the question so yes
是的，我回答这个问题，所以是
that's definitely one of the missing
那绝对是失踪者之一
features in the spring blueprint
春天蓝图的功能
configuration when you compare it to
与之比较时的配置
using the plain trunk at one
一次使用普通行李箱
configuration which allows in place
配置到位
updates of resources we are going to add
我们将添加的资源更新
this we are also planning to improve the
这我们也计划改善
somewhat hidden but still working what
有点隐藏，但仍在工作
for the spring boot dev tools which
用于Spring Boot开发工具
allows much more than just reloading
不仅可以重新加载
resources or view files namely it allows
资源或查看文件，即允许
you to replace code on the fly and in
您可以随时随地替换代码
most ways we are still discussing how to
我们仍在讨论大多数方法
do this properly but there are
正确地做到这一点，但有
definitely plans to Buddhism
绝对打算佛教
of things young looks like we have no
年轻的事情看起来我们没有
more questions at the moment it's
目前有更多问题
if-if-if some some of you still have
如果-如果-如果你们中有些人仍然
questions feel free to ask them in
可以随时提问
Twitter or just share them in comments
Twitter或在评论中分享
tall blog post where we will publish
高大的博客文章，我们将在其中发布
their equipment so I think that's it
他们的设备，所以我认为就是这样
Thanks Jana and Stefan for great
感谢Jana和Stefan的出色表现
presentation and thanks everyone for
演讲，谢谢大家
watching us
看着我们